<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, There!! on Kuldeep saini</title>
    <link>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi, There!! on Kuldeep saini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Mall Customer Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Malls or shopping complexes are often indulged in the race to increase their customers and hence making huge profits. To achieve this task machine learning is being applied by many stores already. It is amazing to realize the fact that how machine learning can aid in such ambitions. The shopping complexes make use of their customers’ data and develop ML models to target the right ones. This not only increases sales but also makes the complexes efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Yearly amount spend Ecommerce</title>
      <link>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>For this Ecommerce project I built a Linear Regression model to identify the yearly spend on various Platform. This could be useful for someone who is new to Ecommerce business from a certain country. This is the underlying model for building something with those capabilities.
I was able to get the model to predict the yearly amount spend of the Ecommerce business with the MAE(Mean Absolute Error) is 7.2 without any minimal tuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Predict mileage per gallon(MPG)</title>
      <link>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Project Description: The following project aims to predict mileage per gallon(MPG) using various technical specifications (features) as input to the regression algorithms.
Database Description: The data is technical spec of cars. This dataset is a slightly modified version of the dataset provided in the StatLib library. In line with the use by Ross Quinlan (1993) in predicting the attribute &amp;ldquo;mpg&amp;rdquo;, 8 of the original instances were removed because they had unknown values for the &amp;ldquo;mpg&amp;rdquo; attribute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuldeepsaini06.github.io/Home/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to look around, check out my portfolio, or get in touch
   Platform URL     Twitter: https://twitter.com/kuldeepsaini06   LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kuldeepsaini06   GitHub: https://github.com/kuldeepsaini06   Facebook: http://facebook.com/kuldeepsaini06    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
